Võ Thành Nhơn (1994), Software Engineer

mail@tedvo.dev | (+84) 793 090994 | Thu Duc, Ho CHi Minh, VN

linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ted-vo | **github:** https://github.com/ted-vo | **Telegram:**

https://telegram.me/ted_vo

SUMMARY

I began my career as an Android Developer, with 4 years of hands-on experience in mobile application development. After that, I transitioned to BackEnd Development, where I worked with NodeJS for 2 years. Currently, I have been working on Site Reliability Engineering (SRE) for 2 years. This progression from mobile development through backend systems to SRE has given me a comprehensive understanding of the software development lifecycle and modern DevOps practices.

EDUCATION

Posts and Telecommunication Institute of Technology, Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

The Degree of Engineer - Software Development

2012-09-05 — 2018-04-01

SKILLS

SRE (*Senior*): GCP, Helm, Cloudflare, Linux, Kubernetes, Shell Script, Terraform, Docker, Golang, Istio, Envoy, Linkerd, DataDog, Grafana, Clickhouse, Elasticsearch, MySQL, Redis, Gitlab CI/CD

Backend Developer (Senior): Java, Nodejs, Golang, Mongodb, SQL, Cryptocurrency, Microservices

Android Developer (*Senior*): Java, Kotlin, Cryptocurrency

EXPERIENCE

Inspirelab | Site Reliability Engineer

2022-04-02 — 2024-11-30

Recognizing my passion for system administration and leveraging my experience from my freelance project, I transition to new position, where I managed infras of new project. I have to learn a lot of new things by 200% of my powers. I susccessful setup infrastructure DEV / PROD environment on Google Cloud Platform.

- I writed terraform code to managed resource from scratch. I have done with modules: VPC Network, IAM, GKE, GCE, Storage, Secret Manager, KMS, CloudRun, CloudSQL, CloudFunction.
- I define Git workflows for developers.
- I used Gitlab CI/CD to build automation system to delivery and deploy applications.
- I writed helm-chart to manage configurations and deloyment Golang application. Optional built-in with sidecar: sevicemesh (Istio, Linkerd), Redis, DataDog.
- I writed shell script develop internal tools for Backend Developer setup local environment. Limit and grant permission to access dev environment and internal apps.
- I monitor GCP resources to balance workloads per nodes and reduce cost.
- I research OpenObserve to planning drop DataDog for optimize cost.
- I also contribute to architecture Backend Systems.

Inspirelab | Back End Developer

2021-06-02 — 2022-04-01

Due to a change in company direction, I transitioned to a Backend Developer role, where I maintained two critical projects.

- Language using is Java (17)
- I maintain and develop new feature of Initial coin offering (ICO) system.
- I develop user referral feature
- I develop reward cryptocurrency pool prize for game portal.
- I fixed critical bug of forgot password feature.

Inspirelab | Android Leader

2021 - 04 - 19 - 2021 - 06 - 01

Form new Android team with 2 members to build super application for gaming platform.

- Structure architecture of the super application like Grab but for gaming.
- Manage and assign tasks for team member.
- I develop blockchain payment SDK for App in App

Vitalify Asia | Android Developer

2019-10-10 — 2021-04-15

https://vitalify.asia

Maintenance and develop outsoure projects

- Maintenance Golf Club application.
- Develop new healthcare application. The application sync data from healthcare device via BLE.
- Maintenance SDK of the ads ecosystem. The SDKs contact with the device via BLE. Restruct the new version of SDK with simple integration and high-performance.
- Develop the new plugin SDK for application build with Cordova.

Finance Technology Solutions | Android Developer

2019-03-01 — 2019-09-01

Develop new features

• Develop tradingviews and charts for cryptocurrency application. Stockchart (time-line, k-line, macd, kdj, rsi...)

Horical | Fullstack Developer

2017-09-01 - 2019-02-28

Maintenance a outsoure project and develop 2 product projects

- Maintenance car fixing service application.
- Develop Coffee-shop management system.
- Develop ERP client android application.

LANGUAGES

Vietnamese (*Native*), **English** (*Good at read and writing. Limited at speaking*)

.....

INTERESTS

Computer [Computer Science , Open Source] , Fitness [Hiking/Camping] , Music [Drums , Guitar]